greatapps.com 2014-10-04

# GreatApps.com | Great Apps | Apps | Market your app | App Discovery | App Marketing | iOS | iPhone | iPad | Android | Windows | Google Play | BlackBerry

Thank you for visiting the GreatApps.com Web site (hereinafter “the Site” or “GreatApps.com”) and reviewing our Privacy Policy, effective October 4, 2011. We take your privacy very seriously and are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use GreatApps.com. 

#### Overview

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter “Policy”) governs your use of GreatApps.com and describes the information we collect from you and what may happen to that information. For example, this Policy will let you know what information we collect from you; what cookies are and how they are used; how your information is used; who is collecting your information; with whom your information may be shared; what options are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information; how you may use other users’ information ("Users"); the types of security precautions in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of your information; how we protect children’s privacy; and what else you should know about your online privacy. 

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that our practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. All amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted on the Site. 

By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Site. 

#### What Personally Identifiable Information does GreatApps.com collect?

The primary purpose of collecting information from you is to allow you to create an account with us so that you can take advantage of all of the tools and features provided on the Site and to provide you with a personalized experience. We will only collect information about you that we consider necessary to achieve this purpose. 

Generally, GreatApps.com collects personally identifiable information in two ways. Some information is gathered when you register so that you may receive notifications regarding new apps posted to the Site. This includes your name, your email, and a self-selected password. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. Please note that registration is NOT required to view the Site but is required to access all of the features and tools of the Site. It's your decision whether you want to share personally identifiable information with us. We also collect personal information when you report a problem or issue with our services through the Site’s feedback form or contact form. If you contact GreatApps.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

Wherever GreatApps.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

#### What are IP Addresses and how does GreatApps.com use them?

When your web browser requests a web page from another computer on the Internet, such as GreatApps.com, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet protocol.") For many users accessing the Internet, the IP address will be different every time you log on. We record the IP Addresses that access GreatApps.com along with related information such as your browser type and operating system. This information helps us, in part, learn about the geographical distribution of our website visitors and the technology they use to access our site so that we can improve our Site. 

#### What are “cookies” and how does GreatApps.com use them?

Data collection devices, such as “cookies,” are used to store, and sometimes track, information about you. Generally, these cookies help provide personalized services and promote trust and safety. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer’s hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the Site where you are prompted to login or that are customizable request that you accept cookies. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. Most cookies are “session cookies,” and are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. 

More specifically, we use cookies to remind us of who you are and to access your registration information in order to deliver to you a more personalized service. This cookie is set when you register or “Log In” and is modified when you “Log Out” of our services. We also may use cookies to measure your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this data to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on GreatApps.com a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our Site. You are always free to decline our cookies if you wish and if your browser permits, however please know that you may not be able to Log In if you choose not to accept our cookies. 

#### How does GreatApps.com use my information?

GreatApps.com uses your information to provide you with a customized website experience. We may also use your personal information to manage and monitor your registration with us; communicate with you via email if we need to contact you; resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe interactions between users of GreatApps.com; detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity; and enforce our Terms of Service Agreement. 

#### Who is collecting information?

When you are using the Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with GreatApps.com alone, unless we specifically state otherwise. We do not sell or rent your information to third parties. 

Please be advised that GreatApps.com app providers, advertisers, sponsors, or Web sites that have links on our Site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you interact with them. The information practices of those Web sites linked to GreatApps.com are not covered by this privacy statement and you should be sure to check the policies of those Web sites to before disclosing your personal information to them. 

#### With whom does GreatApps.com share my information?

We understand that your privacy is important. Generally, GreatApps.com will not disclose your personally identifiable information unless we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as those described below. 

When the Law Requires it: If we receive a subpoena, court order, or other legal process that requires that we disclose information about a User, we have no choice but to comply with it and will disclose the required information. 

Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate: Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas and services of the Site. Aggregate data may be disclosed in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, no personal information that could be used to identify you personally is disclosed in these situations. 

External Service Providers: Separate services are offered by third parties, also known as external service providers, some of whom advertise on the Site. If you choose to use these services, disclose information to these parties, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, their privacy policy governs the use of your information. We will not disclose your personal information to external service providers without your express consent. 

Business Transaction: GreatApps.com reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with the Site, to a third party in the event of a sale or other transfer of assets or of any portion of our business. In the event GreatApps.com enters a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information may be among the assets transferred. 

Other: We may disclose account information where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating GreatApps.com’s Terms of Service Agreement or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) GreatApps.com’s rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. GreatApps.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our services. 

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, as stated above, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. We use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

#### What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?

You do not have to disclose personally identifiable information to view the Site. If you choose to register on the Site, you will need to disclose certain information as specified above. GreatApps.com will send you email upon registration with the Site. GreatApps.com may also send you email from time to time. Only GreatApps.com, or agents working on behalf of GreatApps.com, will send you these emails. 

#### How may I use other users’ information?

User contact information, such as email address, is not generally disclosed on the Site to other Users. However, in the event that you obtain the contact information of a User or Users of Site, you agree that you not use such information for any purpose. Further, recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside. 

Finally, we do not tolerate spam. You are not licensed to add us, or a GreatApps.com User, even one who contacted you, to your mail (email or physical mail) list without the express, written consent of that User. 

#### What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

Your GreatApps.com registration information is password protected so that only you have access to this personal information. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. GreatApps.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or unsolicited email. If you choose to share your email address (which is used as your log-in name) and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

Whenever GreatApps.com handles your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service Agreement and this Policy. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

#### How are children’s privacy protected?

GreatApps.com is not designed or intended for persons under the age of 13 and, if you are under the age of 13, you are not authorized to use the Site, submit information to GreatApps.com, or register with us. If you are between the age thirteen and eighteen, you may use the Site and register with us with the prior permission and authorization of your parent or guardian. Persons under the age of 13 are prohibited from viewing the Site, submitting any comments, or submitting any personal information to us, regardless of parental or guardian approval. We do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. 

#### Additional Information

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to us through the use of our Contact page, which can be found at <http://greatapps.com/contact>. 

This Policy is the sole authorized statement of GreatApps.com’s practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information.
